http://www.salk.edu/privacy-policy

Salk Institute for Biological StudiesPrivacy PolicySalk Institute for Biological Studies -
Salk Institute for Biological Studies	-
Privacy PolicyHome - Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThe Salk Institute for Biological Studies (“Salk”) values our donors, job applicants, volunteers and all on-line visitors (collectively, “Visitors”) and is committed to respecting and protecting their privacy. It does not sell, trade or rent information it collects from them with other organizations or use that information to make mailings on behalf of other organizations. Salk provides the opportunity to those who do not wish to be publicly acknowledged to be recognized anonymously. Within Salk, we limit access to this information to circumstances that require such access.Information Salk collects includes personal information that is voluntarily provided by Visitors, including electronically, and information that is publicly available. The types of personally identifiable information collected may include a Visitor’s name, home, work and email address, telephone and fax number, credit card information, date of birth, gender, qualifications, educational and work history and expertise. The Salk uses that information to accept donations and applications for employment and to inform our donors and prospects about news and activities of the Salk, upcoming events and our fundraising needs, to thank donors and distribute receipts, and to make reports to U.S. and state agencies as required by law.We may need to disclose this personal information to third party vendors to process, analyze and/or store data for us. We try to ensure that these entities do not use personal information for any other purpose, and that they have agreed to maintain the confidentiality and integrity of the information they obtain from us.The Salk also collects certain traffic data information such as an on-line Visitor’s IP address, domain server, type of computer and type of web browser. This is anonymous information that does not personally identify the Visitor but is helpful for purposes of improving the experience on our website.We provide links from our websites to other websites that we believe may be of interest to our on-line Visitors. Please be aware that those sites may collect information. This policy does not apply to, and cannot control, those other websites.This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes.We will remove anyone who requests deletion from our mailing lists. If you wish to be removed or have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at info@salk.edu.(Last updated October, 2010.)
